One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
Our world’s gonna be
in the hands of pirates?!
Wait a minute...
What are you telling us, Vegapunk?!
No! Will our country
sink into the sea, too?!
Do something, Marines!
The world’s greatest genius confirmed it!
Let’s go get it!
The One Piece is real!
Pirates are going to rule the world!
That’s what the world
sank into the sea for, right?!
Brace yourselves, World Government!
Why are we allowing this broadcast?!
Transponder Snails around the prison
are broadcasting it!
We don’t have a way to stop them!
How could he say that?!
Vegapunk!
Luffy...
I...
I’m...
gonna be King of the Pirates!
Whaaa?!
Th-Th-The King of the Pirates is the person...
who obtains everything this world has to offer!
That means...
you’re talking about
seeking the One Piece!
I...
have to stop you
from achieving your dream!
Buggy! Buggy!
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Chairman Buggy!
Show us...
the world you’re going to create!
Buggy! Buggy!
Buggy...
My world, you say?
You absolute idiots...
That ain’t what I’m after!
What? Chairman Buggy...
It’s our world... Right?
Buggy! Buggy!
Chairman Buggy!
We’ll follow you,
even to the depths of hell!
Buggy! Buggy!
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Sit.
Yes, sir...
Caribou?
What do you want us to do, Teach?
We’re fine with killing him, if you want...
W-Wait a minute!
The information I’ve got is sure to please ya,
Master Teach!
Bring him to me.
Yes, sir!
And if what he has to say
doesn’t blow me away...
we blow him away.
That’s the truth.
Joyboy is...
his...
The Void Fortnight
Iron giant!
It’s that horse-gramps again!
Nooo! Do something, Zoro!
I’m sorry, Joyboy...
You okay?! Giant Robo!
I wanted to apologize!
Deep down, I knew...
that you couldn’t still be alive...
Are you mixing me up with someone else?
But...
You look so much like him...
It brings back...
what I felt that day.
An earthworm monster!
We can’t escape! The ship’s gonna sink!
I’m sorry...
Joyboy...
That I couldn’t make you king...
“King”?
You...
What’s your name?
I’m...
Monkey D. Luffy!
The man who’ll become the King of the Pirates!
“D”...
Hey, Luffy...
Conqueror's haki?
Thank you...
for letting me hear the old rhythm...
that I miss so much.
Don’t die, okay?
I won’t...
let you die!
Haki?!
And it’s ridiculously strong...!
Whose is it?!
Great Imu!
Joyboy!
Guys!
You’re all right!
Luffy!
I’m so glad we made it down safe!
You’re the best, Jinbe!
Made it by the skin of our teeth!
We’re alive!
Thought I was gonna die!
I’m still not sure I believe we’re safe...
Luffy! What happened
to those monsters?!
Uhh, dunno...
They disappeared...
What’s goin’ on?
A robot used haki?!
How can haki make people disappear?!
Nami!
Are you okay?!
We’re fine!
But Atlas and Edison...
Listen, Emet...
Only when the time is right.
Time is right?
I tied a knot of my greatest Haki...
and sealed it inside of you!
You’re going to keep on living
long after I’m gone.
The day’ll come
when I can no longer help you.
What? No way...
When your life’s in danger...
When someone you want to
protect is in danger...
That’s when the time is right!
Untie the knot then!
When the time is right...
you’ll save me...
That’s right!
I’ll reach out and help you
from the past!
Just like I always do!
I’m glad!
Thank you!
Then even after your death,
its like you’re still here with me!
Hey, now! This is far
into the future now, got that?
I’ll never, ever...
ever...
be lonely!
Egghead! Come in!
What the hell’s going on?!
Captains!
Hey! Find out what happened to ‘em!
Aye-aye, Captain!
Amazin’!
That was conqueror’s haki, right?!
Ya knocked out both
the monsters and the Marines!
You're pretty cool, Robo!
Captains!
All of ‘em really are out cold!
Are they? I can’t believe it!
I couldn’t sense any hostility!
Could it be better than what Red Hair can do?
How long are you all going to
keep sleeping?! Get up!
You will take Us away from here!
Wake up, you imbeciles!
The Straw Hats are escaping!
We owe ya one for savin’ us!
Thanks a lot,
Giant Robo!
See ya later!
All right! While they’re napping...
let’s make ourselves scarce!
You got it,
Captains!
Let’s get goin’, boys!
To Elbaph!
Set sail!
We’re goin’ to Elbaph!
Welcome back, Luffy!
Luffy!
I’m pooped...
Huh?! You look terrible!
Hey, Straw Hat! You okay?!
We still got Hákarl if ya want!
Masters!
Thank you so much for coming!
I missed you guys!
Thank you all!
Follow us, folks!
Don’t be slowpokes about it, now!
Oh, yeah! I finally get to go to Elbaph!
Jinbe!
Aye! Full speed ahead it is!
Let's get the dance floors
of the world bouncing, folks!
We've got a fresh setlist of tracks!
Incite fear!
Paint the worst possible future!
Make ‘em hang on our every word!
All they can do is wait for the next WEJ!
Actual scum.
Vegapunk was offering us hope as well!
Stay off my stage, kiddo!
Or I’ll expose your whereabouts!
Oh, have I offended you,
Mr. Big-Lie-Spreading Birdbrain?
The wise won’t dance
to the tune of your lies!
First of all, you...
Now, now, dear Vivi...
Why don’t we calm down...
Make him angry, and he’s gonna
put us out on the streets!
You’re right. The truth can be
interesting, sometimes...
So what if the world sinks into the sea?
The sky’s my home!
In that sense, it’s the dawning of my era!
Say, Your Royal Highness...
Maybe you oughta rethink
how you’re treating me, eh?
Like I care? If the world’s ending,
I’m not putting my survival above anyone else’s!
Hey, Vivi, you’ve really gotta...
Check this out! We’ve got another
mountain of shocking news!
Emperor Blackbeard
versus Trafalgar Law!
Emperor Red Hair
versus Eustass “Captain” Kid!
Emperor Straw Hat Luffy
kills Vegapunk!
You’re a liar!
Come in!
What the hell’s going on?!
I want to know
what the hell that broadcast was!
I want a sitrep yesterday!
Come in, dammit!
Are they all dead?
What the hell happened, Egghead?!
You’re quite loud, you know.
Why are you the one answering?
Borsalino! What happened to
the other sailors?!
Every single one of them is sleeping.
I don’t see them waking up for a while.
Then what the hell is going on?!
St. Saturn had better be safe!
What about the Power Plant?!
And the fugitives?!
I’ll have a report sent in
once the young’uns wake up.
You’d best not have half-assed your job,
Borsalino!
Let me ask you, Sakazuki...
Have you ever...
killed a close friend of yours?
Your head is huge!
Nice to meet you.
I’m Borsalino, a Marine.
How much can you provide?
Hmm?
My arrest is just an excuse.
You people just want my brain.
How much can you pay
in research funds?
You’re an interesting man!
So this is your plan for the island?
I’m going to call it Egghead!
We're building the future 500 years ahead!
Will you give me a hand, Borsalino?
I can’t, I’m an Admiral now.
Don’t drop it, Uncle!
You ain’t standin’ straight!
I’m counting on you, Borsalino!
This island, Egghead,
is packed to the brim with the fruits of
cutting-edge research from every field of study!
Destroy it, and you’ll set
scientific progress back a hundred years!
Rescind the Buster Call!
Please, Kizaru!
You accuse me of having
“half-assed” my job, Sakazuki...
If you have the time to
sit on your ass and doubt me,
then come take a look with your own
damn eyes, you ungrateful brat!
I’m sorry, brother...
Don’t even start...
I don’t really get it, Vegapunk...
What you said at that moment, I mean.
Is this the result you were shooting for?
C’mon. I couldn’t ask you
what you really meant,
but you said some pretty outrageous stuff.
We’re heading down to save Bonney,
and I’m going to stay down there!
Huh?! But you’d die!
Don’t try to save me.
Just let me die then and there!
Egghead
Two weeks before
the Straw Hats' Arrival
What on...?
This is...!
Stella! Pythagoras!
There are irregularities in the readings
from the Power Plant?!
There is no mistaking it...
Look at the changes in the
particle number density and the neutron flux.
The energy expenditure on the Seraphim
has been slowly incremented over time.
If this is a mistake in our calculations,
it is a grave one.
Oh, oh? These values
don’t match the ones we verified!
The reaction rate is rising...
yet the Power Plant remains stable!
Indeed.
Which means this data is evidence that
someone stole a portion of the Mother Flame.
All the readings with respect to the Power Plant
were carefully manipulated.
The only person capable of this...
is a Vegapunk!
Is it Lilith?!
Now, now, we don’t have
confirmation yet!
Unfortunately,
only we three have airtight alibis.
A vast quantity of energy was stolen.
So you’re saying it’s one of
the remaining four, yes?
Most likely Lilith!
That’s why you had us
put our brains into stealth mode!
Yes, if this experience is shared
with Punk Records, Lili—
the culprit will notice we’ve noticed.
We will absolutely find out
who did this!
Mm-hmm!
Egghead
A week before
the Straw Hats' arrival
Damn! Not a single lead!
Lilith is clean!
All four of them have alibis.
Why can’t we find anything?!
Oh dear! Oh dear! I've identified the culprit!
It’s York!
What?! York?!
The information she synchronized
with Punk Records were dummy memories!
Videos from the Camsnails
on the route she took were also fabricated!
Gimme seconds...
But for what purpose?!
And sorry, Lilith!
There are signs of the Sea Beast Weapons
being manipulated.
Found evidence of use of the White
Transponder Snail to block eavesdropping!
Found it!
Successfully recovered the data
from the Long-Distance Transponder Snail!
Dr. Vegapunk is researching
the Void Century.
What?!
Is this a transmission to Mary Geoise?!
This explains why Cipher Pol
kept coming back to investigate!
Six days before
the Straw Hats' Arrival
I heard the Kingdom of Lulusia vanished!
We don’t have full details yet,
but I do have this sense of dread!
Pythagoras! Keep a close eye
on the radio signals and the groundwater level!
I will!
Does this have something to do
with the stolen Mother Flame?
It does!
She must have transported the Mother Flame via
the Sea Beast Weapons and handed it to the Government.
If I may speculate,
I’d say the Government
possesses the Ancient Weapons!
And they were most likely activated
using the Mother Flame that York gave them.
We’ll soon see the results.
This is the most likely scenario...
Yet I can’t go public with it.
This is all my fault!
Stella...
I should never have isolated greed
from the human mind!
If we apprehend her,
is there anything else we can do?
No, we’re far too late.
Regardless of her objective,
those who study the Void Century
are erased from existence!
She proved her worth to them by
carelessly handing over the Mother Flame.
If it had been us, we would’ve thoroughly
examined their objectives and all aspects of safety!
Stella, we can still escape...
Then I re-quasar you ready a ship!
This is to allow the residents
of Egghead to escape!
But for us, we cannot escape.
Secret orders will have already been
issued to all naval branches.
We’d be chased to the ends of the world.
If we die on the run,
our deaths would be in vain.
But Egghead has resources
that Ohara didn’t, 22 years ago!
It has the means to
maximize the reach of my voice!
Anyway... the closer I get to it,
the darker and more obscure it becomes!
What is the World Government, truly?!
I will die, but it won’t be in vain!
I’m sorry for involving you two.
Don’t be. We’re Vegapunks, too.
We were thinking the same thing!
But, Stella, remember...
Our definition of “death” is unique.
Indeed. There is one other thing
that we must protect...
The Cloud Plant,
the island clouds generator!
Island clouds could play a vital role
in saving mankind in the future.
Whuh?
Stella! Whatcha doin’ here?
Oh, it’s you, York...
The same thing I’m always doing!
An operational experiment
using the Mother Flame!
If we could run this thing with it,
it would be the ideal energy source!
You’re right! I hope ya finish
your experiment soon!
Yup!
Its incomplete state is our only hope.
Two days before
the Straw Hats' Arrival
Go ahead and talk.
I’ve started recording.
Um... Hello?
Check, check...
Hello, world! Come in, world!
I am Dr. Vegapunk!
A humble genius scientist!
It will come as a shock, I’m sure...
But it is the truth,
and all have the right to know!
No one will expect that
the Transponder Snail is hidden in here!
My death will be
the trigger for the broadcast.
And to ensure she doesn’t discover
what we set up, even by the remotest chance,
we’ll wipe it from our memories.
But in exchange,
other memories will also be lost.
We’ll have to find out again that
York stole the Mother Flame and sold us out.
We’ll also realize
that we’re being targeted,
and we will be startled anew.
Very much so.
We’ll experience the terror
as if for the first time.
But, we have already taken measures!
And the utter disaster that awaits
just around the corner...
is none other than
our ultimate triumph!
Shaka, what were we doing?
I don’t know.
Why are we here?
This is our memory mass testing lab...
Perhaps we were conducting a test?
This is my handwriting...
“Good morning, everyone."
"There is now a Void Fortnight
in your memories,"
"but this was by your own choice."
"There are more surprises in store for you,"
"LOL.”
Wha?!
“I’ll share just this with you:"
"The World Government discovered
our research into the Void Century,"
"but I’ve taken
the best possible measures."
"Just trust yourself,"
"and die.”
What?! They found out?!
And you’re telling us to “die”?!
No chance!
“And one more thing..."
What is all this stuff?!
Stella! Emperor Straw Hat’s crew
have arrived, along with Bonney!
What?!
CP-0 has landed!
We’re surrounded by Marine ships!
What?!
It’s Admiral Kizaru
and St. Saturn of the Five Elders!
What?!
We’re heading down to save Bonney,
and I’m going to stay down there!
Huh?! But you’d die!
Don’t try to save me.
Just let me die then and there!
What?! You got a death wish
or something?!
No, but I have this feeling my death
will bring about something significant!
Don’t even joke about that!
I’m protectin’ ya!
Yeah, it’ll cause huge-ass riots!
We can’t let you die!
Pretty please?!
To our reunion with old friends!
Cheers!
Onward to Elbaph!
Onward to my dream!
And you know, about the One Piece...
What are you...?!
I want your crew
to be the ones to get it!
No, wait... Not now, later...
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
piipapii papipo, piipapii
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
no no no no no norenai
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama feel so good, mata unlucky demo
cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no boys & girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no boys & girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran run run run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga punk!!!!!! no way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamine
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru